https://www.integrity-research.com/privacy/

Trending
Mergers and AI are Curing ESG Data’s Ills
Planned Hiring on Wall Street Outstrips Layoffs for 4th Straight Month
ESG Data is Inconsistent, Confusing, Opaque Yet Increasingly Vital
Survey: Buy-Side Value for European Sell-Side Meetings Plunge in 2020
Study: Expert Network Industry Tops $1.5 Billion Despite Muted Growth During Pandemic
ESG Startup Matter Closes Series A Led by Nasdaq
US IPO Activity Dips Sharply in November
S&P Global Agrees to Pay $44 bln for IHS Markit
Despite Faltering European Revenues, Capital Economics Posted Revenue Gains in 2019
Search
This privacy policy explains how Integrity Research Associates LLC (“Integrity Research”, “Integrity”, “we” and “us”) collects, uses, shares and protects information obtained from visitors to its websites (each, a “Site” and collectively, the “Sites”).
Personal Information and Other Data We Collect
Integrity Research collects information that you voluntarily provide to us, including your name and contact details. Integrity may also collect information from third parties.
When you visit our Sites, we send one or more cookies a small file containing a string of characters to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the Sites during future visits. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)
Integrity Research’s servers automatically record information when you visit our Sites. These servers’ logs include information such as:
Your Internet Protocol or IP address.
The type of browser you are using and/or operating system.
The specific web pages you visited prior to visiting our site and the pages you accessed via our site.
Information you have provided as part of the commenting process on our site.
Specific links that you have clicked through in our site.
Your bandwidth speed and general information about software programs that have been installed on your computer.
Aggregate information that reflects your clickthrough rates and also viewing of any videos on our site.
Server log information aggregated via HTML code or cookies and/or related technologies.
We may access information about you that is provided to us by third parties including ad networks, social media sites, databases services, online advertising or marketing companies.
Social media connections to our site may supply your user name, demographic information, click through rates, specific and unique identifiers that can encompass mobile device information that is governed by the applicable law.
Collectively, the information that Integrity Research collects about you, including personal information, is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “your information.”
Use of Your Information
We use your information to process and administer details of your use of the Sites such as registration or permission to access subscription information, and to keep you up to date with new developments at Integrity Research. We also use and analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.
We do not sell or share your personal information obtained through our Sites with third parties for their marketing purposes. Integrity and trusted third parties process personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected.
Integrity Research may contact you using personal information you voluntarily provide.
Disclosure of Your Information
Your information will be held by Integrity Research in the United States and may also be held and accessed by Integrity Research staff and third parties working for Integrity Research, or Integrity Research’s subsidiaries and affiliates, inside and outside the United States. If your information is gathered outside the United States, it may be transferred to Integrity Research’s United States offices to be used for these purposes.
Integrity Research may disclose your information in response to legal process, to protect our rights, as otherwise required by law, or for the prevention or detection of a crime. If we sell our company or part of it, or our business enters into a joint venture with another business entity, Integrity Research may disclose your information to our new business partners or owners who may then provide you with information about their products and services.
Accessing & Updating Your Information
You are entitled to see the personal information held about you, subject to Integrity Research’s confidentiality obligations to its clients. You may also request that we make changes to your personal information so that it is accurate and kept up to date, and we may update your information using data obtained from third parties.
Your Ability to Opt-Out of Information Collection & Use and Set E-mail Preferences
You may choose not to provide personal information to Integrity Research.
You may set up your computer to reject cookies. However, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our Sites.
We may send you emails to share news and invite you to events. If you do not wish to receive any of these emails, you may click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the emails. Please note that whatever your preferences, we may still contact you regarding your business relationship with Integrity.
Content Forwarding
Integrity Research may provide tools on the Sites to forward content from the Sites to others through e-mail or other means. E-mail addresses that you supply for content forwarding will be used for that purpose only.
Links
Our Sites may contain links to other web sites belonging to third parties. Please make sure when you leave our Sites that you have read that web site’s privacy policy as this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected at our Sites.
Changes to This Policy
Integrity Research may update this policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted to the Sites. Your continued use of these Sites will indicate your agreement to such changes.
Contact
All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to the following e-mail address privacy@integrity-research.com.
